Based on the true story of Moe Berg
The Catcher Was a Spy is a drama, war, thriller film directed by Ben Lewin.
Former major league baseball player Moe Berg lives a double life working
for the Office of Strategic Services in World War II Europe.
Moe Berg, played by Paul Rudd.
Werner Heisenberg, played by Mark Strong.
Estella Huni, played by Sienna Miller.
Koranda, played by Connie Nielsen.
Joe Cronin, played by Shea Whigham.
Kawabata, played by Hiroyuki Sanada.
The Catcher Was a Spy is a 2018 American war film directed by Ben Lewin and written by
Robert Rodat, based on the book of the same name by Nicholas Dawidoff.
It stars Paul Rudd as Moe Berg, a former baseball player who joined the war
effort during World War II and participated in espionage for the U.S.
Government.
Mark Strong, Sienna Miller, Jeff Daniels, Tom Wilkinson, Giancarlo Giannini,
Hiroyuki Sanada, Guy Pearce, and Paul Giamatti also star.
The film premiered at the 2018 Sundance Film Festival, and
was released on June 22, 2018, by IFC Films.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
espionage, spy, baseball, world war ii.
The tone is emotional and intense.